When did you know him?
Ah, Rodtang.
I just met him a moment ago.
Tee, why aren't you with your friends?
Or are you gonna hit on Fuse?
Can I?
Ayy.
Didn't you get a tattoo for other people to look at?
The reason I got it...
is none of your business.
Do you think...
someone can kiss a person that they aren't into?
You can punch me.
Because I feel really good.
One, two.
Three, four, five.
Six.
Seven, eight.
Nine, ten.
Like this.
Who wants to try?
Me, me.
Great, come here.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Hey.
Don't rush or force it.
Find the right tempo.
Tempo?
Baby shark tempo.
(Singing "Baby Shark".)
He's still unconscious.
I think I have to do rescue breathing.
Only CPR is enough.
Where did you go?
I did some paperwork for Teacher Lookmee.
Hey, lie down.
Okay.
Next person.
Are you feeling hot?
Yeah. I also want to take a pee.
The bathroom is even broken.
Yeah, I have to use the bathroom on the second floor.
You know what? On the second floor…
a bathroom window is really huge.
I saw someone kissing on other’s cheek.
Fuse, you okay? I'll give you CPR.
Great, do it like that.
Did you tell anyone?
I did.
Hey.
I told you.
I mean someone else.
If you don’t want me to tell others,
pay me.
What do you want?
I want the truth.
About Tee and you.
We’re friends.
Friends?
But I have never kissed your cheek.
We’re friends.
I haven’t broken up with Jeen yet.
It’s good that you know.
If you don’t want any trouble,
you should sort things out one by one.
Think carefully before you do anything.
But if you get stuck,
let me know.
- Hey.
You’re playing without us?
Yeah, you’re playing without me.
Come here, be my team.
Let’s tag team.
Come on.
Son, I know why you tripped.
What?
Because you kept looking at Fuse.
Good thing Teacher Bangjong's cake didn't drop.
Or…
Should I give Fuse a cake?
Eh? Won’t you have it?
I want to see him smiles to me.
Damn. Go for it.
Tee.
Sorry, I'm hungry.
Give yours to me then.
What is mine,
it is mine.
Got it?
Tee.
Where are they rushing off to?
Teacher Banjong’s cake is really tasty.
Have you eaten it?
Yeah.
When did you eat it?
It is still on the table.
Tee.
This cake is not only yours.
No matter how much you want to keep it,
if the owner comes to claim it,
you have to return it.
Got it?
You mean Teacher Banjong will get the cake back?
Frame isn't picking up my call at all.
Yeah.
He might be busy.
What about going to Siam today?
Why?
Because our school band performs today.
Fuse, are you skipping a class?
You kidding? It's you who skipped a class.
I didn't. I'm practice for
the show at Siam this evening.
Will you come to see a show?
Ah.
So, will you go?
Nah, I have drum major practice.
We'd better go.
Go, let's go.
Line up.
Go.
Hmph.
Forward, March.
Shit, I think juniors stand us up.
Hey, guys.
Please split up to find them.
Yeah, please help us.
Sup. Where should I practice?
Oh, you're coming for real?
Eh? Why?
I'm sorry.
I forgot to tell you that you don't need to come.
Uh… the first drum major is not free.
I'll reschedule your practice later.
Alright, it's fine.
And don't feel down.
Since you are already here,
sit around and chill out.
Fine.
Alright.
Can I have some encouragement?
Are you close to him?
Nah.
Nah? He was looking at you.
(Fuse, where are you? I'm at your door.)
What? Why did she go there?
I gotta go.
Okay.
Hey, where did Fuse go?
Uh… I don't know.
I need to use the restroom.
Then…
I'll go with you.
To help me carry it?
To help you hold it.
Don't you feel drained?
Mr. Narongsak, please go to
examination room number four.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Can I come with him?
Are you a relative of the patient?
I'm his boyfriend.
I'm actually his boyfriend.
I'll kiss him as proof if you don't believe it.
That's fine.
This way, please.
Okay.
Let's go.
That hurts.
Hey.
What?
I'm just holding it.
Are you having dirty thoughts?
Or do you want to do it?
Stop it.
Let's go.
Fine, then I'll do it like a train.
Choo-choo, okay?
Yinwan, are you making a cake?
Yes, since Mr. Tim said he wanted it.
But I also made it for you.
Thank you.
But you have to wait a sec.
Let me decorate it first.
You can choose whatever you want.
What are you looking at?
Uh.
I'm looking at the cake.
It looks delicious.
Well, can I do it myself?
Of course.
But… who did you make this cake for?
He is a very adorable person.
Why do you have to dress so properly?
I don't want him to find out
that I went back home to do it.
You shy?
That's cute.
I bet he'll be so happy.
Really?
That's good if these make him happy.
Well, I have to go now.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Jeen.
Fuse.
Have you been here for a while?
Why didn’t you tell me you were coming?
If I told you, would you let me come?
Right, are Pa and Ma at home?
No.
Well… can I come in and get some water?
I’ll get you some water.
Fuse.
I think we need to talk.
Why didn’t you reply my messages?
And you don’t pick up my call either.
Why don’t you play some sports?
So cool.
I’m gonna leave.
(Real time pics, bro.)
I have a dinner plan with my mom.
I just saw Jeen.
She walked with the same man.
Where did you see them?
At BTS.
You seems different these days.
Are you okay?
I think we should break up.
What’s going on with you?
Why have you changed this much?
If there is something,
why can’t you just say it to my face?
Am I still your girlfriend to you?
Can we not break up?
I love you so much, Fuse.
I don’t want things to turn out this way.
Do you still love me?
I love you.
Why, Fuse?
We’re a couple.
We’ve been fine without doing it.
That’s why we’re not even like a couple.
I know.
You’re a gentleman.
And you have always respected me.
But I’m your girlfriend.
If you love me,
you must not push me away.
There are only two of us now.
You can do whatever you want to.
Wanna try?
I’d like to know how it feels too.
But there are some of them who don’t punch.
What if they don’t punch…
because they also like it?
I guess people like us,
if we let some one kiss us,
that person must be very special.
Fuse, I bought you a cake.
Shall we try?
I just want to know how to do it.
Don’t ask anyone to try this again.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
Tee.
I’m sorry for interrupting you.
I’ll put it outside.
But… who did you make this cake for?
I bet he'll be so happy.
Tee.
Fuse.
I’m leaving now.
Too bad we got interrupted today.
Let's try it again next time.
Well, will your friend tease you about this tomorrow?
Tell me when you arrived.
Um, okay.
Bye.
Ah.
Okay.
Good job.
You have taken it.
It’s time for bed.
Here.
Lie down.
Okay, pull the blanket up.
Sleep. It’s already 8 PM.
Who goes to sleep at 8 PM?
Ah.
Okay.
If you don’t sleep at 8 PM, you’ll not recover.
If you’re not recover,
I’ll be here and take care of you.
Privately.
I know you're addicted to me.
Do you want to catch a cold?
A cold? That’s nothing to me.
I won’t catch a cold.
Go back, please.
Fine.
I’ll go back.
But I’m waiting for you to fall asleep.
Or else you’ll sneakily be on your phone again.
You can sleep, I’ll take care of you.
Sleep.
Wanna see it? Take my phone.
Are you hooking up with many people?
Me?
Well…
Quite a lot.
What about you? Do you hook up often?
Never.
What?
What about when you meet me?
Don’t tell me that I’m the first.
For real, Book?
It’s 8 PM now.
I should go to sleep.
Book, seriously, am I the first?
Book, tell me before you sleep.
Sleeping at 8:30 PM is fine.
Tell me first.
Am I the first person?
Damn.
I am the first person.
I’m gonna sleep.
Damn.
I’m the first.
I'm Book's first.
Am I really the first person?
Well…
I’ll be dreaming of you.
(Is it wrong to kiss my girlfriend?)
(Grade 11 student kissing inside the house.)
What?
Is it wrong?
Everybody, stand up.
Let's do some activity. We'll play a rondo. Team up.
Fuse, wanna play?
Hey, can we play with you guys?
The new one should be a chaser.
You should be a chaser. Go, go.
Frame, are you having a cold?
No way.
Who catch a cold?
A cold is only for a weak person.
Oh man.
Pass it.
Give it to me.
I'm available. Come on.
What is he doing?
What's going on?
Fuse, come on. Fuse.
I'm available, Fuse.
Give it to me.
Fuse.
Damn, I'm out.
That's boring.
Did you catch a cold from me?
I’m not.
But I’m addicted to you instead.
Then follow me.
May I go to the bathroom, please?
Sure.
Teacher.
May I go to the bathroom, please?
I have a stomachache.
You too? Fine, hurry back then.
Yeah, I don't think you did anything wrong.
Hey, not me.
Right, Robert Sae-tang.
Don’t you think it’s normal?
Just a couple kissing each other.
But what I found strange is...
why Robert think he did something wrong?
Eh?
Don’t you think he care…
Bas.
Yeah.
Don’t you think he cares Bas way too much?
If it were other friends…
and faced that situation,
would you be stressed or laugh?
Well…
If you don’t care about it,
just let it go.
But if you do care about it,
you should hurry and sort things out.
That’s better than worrying about it like this.
Hey.
Not me.
It’s Robert Sae-tang.
Yeah, Robert Sae-tang.
Alright.
Hey, I gotta go.
What should I do with Tee?
Can I talk to you?
Sounds a bit aggressive.
Tee, can I talk to you?
Too timid.
Tee, I’ve got something.
Fuse.
Are you okay?
You good?
You okay?
I’m okay.
Are you okay?
Fuse.
Did you throw it?
Yeah.
Ouch.
My head hurts.
It suddenly hurts.
Hey, hey.
Ouch.
Hey, Fuse.
Hey, Tee.
Hurry, take my friend to the nurse’s room.
Hey, take him to the nurse’s room.
Ouch.
He can’t take the pain.
Oh.
Is he okay?
Ouch.
Hey.
What are you waiting for?
Take him to the nurse’s room.
Ouch, I can’t stand the pain.
Ouch, it hurts.
Hey, hurry up.
Ouch.
Hurry up.
I can’t take it.
Ouch.
Tee.
Tee, let me explain.
Here.
The teacher is not here.
Just use a compress for now.
Tee, let me explain.
Yesterday,
there was really nothing.
When you left,
Jeen also left my house.
We didn’t do anything.
So, that’s what you want to explain.
Why did you tell me about it?
Well…
Keep using a compress.
I’d better go now.
Tee.
This cake is not only yours.
No matter how much you want to keep it,
if the owner comes to claim it,
you have to return it. Got it?
Tee.
I'm sorry...
if I hurt your feelings.
It's my fault.
For thinking I had a chance.
About yesterday, it's not your fault at all.
But I think I need to step back.
Can you not step back?
If I kissed you right now,
would we still be friends?